Andrés?
Why are you naked?
Someone could come. It's a heritage site.
No one's coming. I bought all the tickets.
I'm absorbing the stone's telluric energy.
Come.
Lie down. Come on. Lie down.
Lie down.
Did you know the rock under this castle
has magical properties?
The Knights Templar
built this place in the 13th century.
Their buildings were always special sites.
Energy portals, little brother.
This was also the home of Pope Luna.
A rejected, excommunicated man
during insalubrious times,
when life expectancy was under 40,
yet he lived to 94.
How is that possible?
I'll tell you.
Because this rock
has healing energy.
Healing?
Sergio!
What are you thinking?
I'm not one of those
who make their family travel
to give them bad news.
I only bring wonderful news.
Little brother…
I'm getting married.
Again?
Your fourth time,
and you're madly in love.
Even more than before.
Let me guess. You just met her.
Almost.
- Don't you think that's a gift?
- I think it's unlikely.
Sergio! Happiness belongs to he who loves.
Being loved is just a placebo for cowards.
The true nature of love
is in taking action.
Loving like a dog.
And I have that gift.
Isn't it wonderful?
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
But first, today we celebrate
my bachelor party.
Together.
Did you bring summer clothes
or just this librarian suit?
- Well…
- Go buy something.
I have to visit the Dutchman.
Are you buying art?
Something like that.
I've thought it over.
The answer is no.
Please, not so loud.
I don't want to wait until you're done
and let this wave of passion pass me by.
I only asked for time
to do things the right way.
Who knows what'll happen
when you stop working for my husband?
Maybe… I won't want this anymore.
Or you won't want me.
Or maybe…
you'll be shot dead.
Or maybe, despite all your predictions,
we could be happy.
Am I interrupting?
I wish you'd come in two seconds ago.
This man
tried to kiss me.
Darling, would you give us a moment?
Look me in the eye.
Tell me you didn't kiss my wife.
I didn't even try.
You have my word.
I know that's the truth.
We're going through a rough patch.
She pretends we're not, but I notice it.
I… notice everything.
Everything.
And you're here.
Someone we trust. A friend.
Which makes you perfect bait
to feed that fantasy.
Anyway, I know when a man lies.
Now, listen.
If you ever think about touching my wife,
if you brush against her,
or even breathe the same air as her,
I swear to God
you won't leave this palace.
I'll bury you in the crypt with the twins.
Alive.
But I'll leave you a little hole.
Just a tiny one.
So you can breathe for a few days
and have more
than enough time to regret it.
Do you hear me?
Very well.
First cocktail.
All right, tell me.
Who is she?
Her name's Candela.
An ode to life.
- What does she do?
- She's a thief.
We hatched a plan together.
But relax. Don't worry.
It's a fake robbery.
A fake robbery?
An aristocrat. Insufferable man.
He hired me to steal a painting.
I said yes, but I won't do it.
You won't honor the deal?
Not for lack of ideas. Quite the contrary.
Stealing art
is the easiest thing there is.
Andrés.
- Good afternoon.
- Hi. How are you?
Robbing the Bank of Spain,
that's difficult.
It isn't about difficulty.
You gave your word. That's what matters.
Values, Andrés.
Sergio, come here.
That man will want me dead
when he opens his safe
and realizes his dream painting
was just a cover to steal all his money.
Andrés, he may be an aristocrat,
but he's still a criminal.
Do you want to live
forever thinking every door
hides a hitman coming for you?
The only way to stay safe
is to give him something to gain
and something to lose.
If he comes after you,
he must lose much more
than he could ever gain.
- Either we both win or we both lose.
- Exactly.
But for that, you must keep your word.
You're absolutely right.
Besides, making a plan
and not executing it,
that's not that stimulating.
This is much better.
Steal that painting.
I'm going to steal
the Lady with an Ermine.
The Leonardo?
How are you going…?
How are you gonna do it?
Why now?
Because there are no lines left to cross.
If your husband's going to kill me,
I'd rather die after kissing you.
And now that I have,
I'm not going to stop.
Ma'am, the duke sent me for his keys.
He left them in the bathroom.
I haven't seen them.
If I find them, I'll bring them down.
He wants them now. You know how he gets.
I'm getting dressed.
I said I'll bring them when I'm done.
Shall I ask the staff to make your bed?
No need.
I can do it myself. Thank you.
Keila, I can't talk.
Just a minute. It's important.
- Did something happen?
- Not yet.
But it will.
I showed up an hour early for a date.
A date? With Bruce?
With Bruce. And Claudio, my lover.
Looks like we're about to be a trio.
I made a pros-and-cons list
for both of them.
But everything is good for both.
Not a great system.
Excuse me, another margarita.
Extra tequila.
Keila, are you okay?
A little tipsy.
Tell me something, Cameron.
When you hooked up with Jimmy…
did you still have doubts?
Did you know if you loved Jimmy or Roi?
I knew perfectly well.
It was Roi.
I was completely in love with him.
Then Jimmy showed up
and shit went sideways.
I went down to see him
with a knot in my stomach.
I thought that feeling was…
because I was about
to see the love of my life.
But I screwed up.
I lost it.
We bar-hopped all night,
he invited me to a concert…
I got swept up in it.
Only after we fucked on the beach
did I realize
that emotion, that knot in my stomach,
it wasn't about seeing Jimmy again.
It was because I knew Roi
was the most important person in my life.
And you know what?
When I got home, loving him like I did…
I wasn't able to tell him that.
Instead, I blamed him for everything.
Tell him that, okay?
If Roi's the love of your life, tell him.
Maybe when I get back, I'll talk to him.
All right. But come back soon, okay?
All right.
I have to go.
Bruce wants us to have
a three-way relationship.
Really?
Honestly, that's a lot for me.
A relationship with two people
is already plenty. Imagine three.
I don't do well
with short-distance things.
And you'll say, "Yes, you do," but no.
I don't do well with those, no.
I mean, I barely know you,
but this might be
the strangest situation I've ever been in.
It's a strange situation.
You walk in as a lover.
And you might leave engaged.
Marrying as a throuple in Las Vegas.
Before we end up in Vegas,
let me say something.
Because I think
I've been pushing you
into something crazy, and it's… not fair.
Keila, I…
I've defended doing this out of love,
out of generosity.
Because it's modern,
loving more than one person.
But it's a lie. Roi opened up my eyes.
What I really am is afraid.
Afraid because it's the first time
I've loved someone this much.
And this absurd
three-way relationship idea
is just me grasping at straws.
Because we all know he's rushing in
like a hurricane, and I am…
I am the one fading out.
So I made a decision.
I'm leaving.
Your margaritas.
But tonight…
we'll have the goodbye we deserve.
All three of us.
No sob stories or sad faces.
Tonight we party.
To the shortest threesome in history.
What do you think?
It's brilliant.
Come here.
Work's over. The party starts now.
This is a bachelor party.
What kind of music is this?
They call it "flamenco chill."
Remember those house parties
with mom's aunts singing as a sextet?
- No, please.
- Yes.
We'll show these amateurs
how it's done California style.
Please, I'm begging…
Come on. Don't do this to me.
So…
I'll get going.
It's been an epic night.
Claudio.
A pleasure.
Keila.
See you around.
Remember Captain Hook?
When he pricks Peter Pan
with his sword on the ship's plank
to push him to the sharks?
Yeah.
Do you feel like Peter Pan
at the end of the plank?
If I made it this far
it's because it's a miracle
to find someone as wonderful as you.
And I had an epiphany.
You realized you love him?
This is the ending I knew about
from the start.
I'm the interloper here.
It's been beautiful.
Everyone deserves
to have a great affair once
just to realize
how amazing their real love is.
Maybe you should run after him.
Watching the sunrise after a night
like this is beautiful.
No doubt. You should marry more often.
You don't do it enough.
I'll get some coffee.
In the end you were right.
It's a shipment of diamonds.
I slipped a phone in the sack.
If they move the cargo, we'll track it.
See? Sometimes doing
only what you're told isn't enough.
Bye, Berlin.
Thanks.
- Everything okay?
- Perfect.
I've got the checkmate move
for that boorish duke.
- Good evening.
- Evening.
Are you all right?
You look a bit seasick.
The storm. I'm not having a good night.
Your friend Cristina called me.
- How is she?
- Fine.
As well as she can be
after you poisoned her.
Now, tell me. What are you doing here?
I'm a thief.
I work on luxury yachts
because passengers
usually carry jewels and valuables.
Brilliant.
Do you work alone?
I don't need anyone else to do what I do.
Let's do one thing.
Let's consider
three possible reasons you're here.
Sit down.
First option, you're a lone thief
who came for jewels
and ended up tearing a hole
in her bed looking for rice.
Give me that phone.
Second option, you're an undercover cop
who came looking to meet an informant.
But I'll rule that one out.
Unlock the cell phone.
Why rule it out?
No cop's dumb enough
to make a hole in a ship.
Third option.
You're part of a crew.
One that somehow knew
what we have on board
and paid you to do the dirty work.
A crew with planet names.
Captain, you're needed on the bridge.
Well, then.
We'll continue this later.
Look at me.
When I get back,
I want the names of your crew.
If not, irreversible hypothermia
awaits you.
You wouldn't believe
how many sailors fall overboard.
It's nuts.
Comrades, friends, good morning.
Do you have a tan?
Yes. You see, I've been reflecting
on the beach.
There's been a change of plans.
We're stealing the Lady with an Ermine.
Why's that?
It's the perfect safe pass
for us to live in peace
for the rest of our lives.
You'll see.
What's that?
The dirty business the duke hides
on his yachts,
the source of his heaps of dirty money,
is diamond smuggling.
Cameron uncovered that.
Diamonds?
Uncut diamonds from the African coast.
Smuggling precious stones is one of
the most profitable criminal trades.
From mines in Botswana and Sierra Leone,
they reach the black market
in tons, usually stolen by workers.
An uncut stone the duke buys
for 100 or 200 dollars,
once cut, can sell for…
- 75,000 euros?
- At least.
And since traffickers
show no mercy to traitors,
we'll honor our deal.
Sorry, we're not robbing
the cash vault anymore?
We are.
Just after we steal the painting.
I want to show you something.
Excuse me, Keila.
Those days preparing the theft
of the Lady with an Ermine
were the happiest of my life.
With that sweet energy love gives you,
Seville's undeniable beauty,
and with my friends beside me,
calculating every possible risk
to prepare the greatest spectacle
in the history of art theft.
No.
After reviewing everything,
Keila and I think we've solved
how to open the final vault door.
Going over the geo-radar data,
we spotted a small notch on it.
A depression about two inches wide.
I saw it myself.
We thought it was
a biometric scanner print,
which would mean silicon and aluminum,
but it's steel.
We're certain it opens
with an electromagnet.
It makes perfect sense.
And it fits
the duke's twisted personality,
An eccentric who swings
between complexity and simplicity.
Exactly. And I've seen it.
He always carries it with his keys.
We just need someone to take it from him.
From his pocket,
barely brushing against him,
with brilliant sleight of hand.
No. Absolutely not.
This time I'm not mixing
business and personal.
I'll talk to her.
Here, the keys.
I hugged the duke to wish him a good trip
and lifted them from his pocket.
You sure he didn't notice?
I didn't steal them. I swapped them.
Where's my hand cream?
- With your permission, Your Grace.
- Come in.
You see…
I have a concern…
I don't trust the people
you've brought here.
Forgive me,
but you sit them at your table and go
down to the stables to sing with them.
Remember why you brought them here, sir.
They are thieves. Not friends.
What are you saying, Santos?
I think they're not stealing
Lady with an Ermine.
They're planning to rob you.
And you?
What do you think?
I go into that library every day
and watch what they're doing.
I think they are stealing it.
Where are you going?
- Where are our guests?
- The library.
- I can't wait any longer.
- What's going on?
Twenty-four hours until the robbery,
and you've told me nothing.
- Nothing!
- What worries you, Your Grace?
That we lack the talent to pull it off
with the brilliance it deserves?
Sharp as ever. And yes.
That's precisely it.
It would be unforgivable
if it weren't the heist of the century.
Understand?
I want people in Seville
talking about it for decades.
I want two full pages
in the Washington Post!
I want newscasts in the Philippines
leading with the Lady with an Ermine.
I understand you all too well.
Then sit down and enjoy the show.
This is the armored truck
that will transport Lady with an Ermine.
Steel walls, 35 millimeters thick.
Shall we play, Your Grace?
How would you open this truck?
Two of them
will do it with thermal lances?
That would take
approximately nine minutes.
Downtown, around noon,
we'll only have a few seconds.
How exciting.
How will you do it?
With their own codes.
You'll be at the airport with binoculars
when they open the truck to load it.
First, it would be very naive of us
to bet it all on one card,
looking through binoculars.
Second, they use a screen
to avoid this kind of mischief.
Bruce.
So, how will you do it?
There is a perfect moment
when the truck is opened.
Forty-eight hours earlier,
in the peace of a hangar,
they check everything
and fill the gas tank.
But by then,
we'll already have four cameras
to see from every angle…
Keila.
The password.
It's…
It's awesome.
Oh, look, darling!
They look like a boy scout troop
posing with their leader.
But they are the most brilliant
criminal minds in the country.
Where will the heist happen?
On the Triana Bridge.
Triana Bridge…
Please,
tell me I can be
at one of those rooftop bars,
watching my magnum opus unfold.
No. You need to be
as far away as possible.
Go to the countryside
with friends who can testify for you.
Above all, don't do any internet searches
related to the Lady with an Ermine.
If you're ever on the list of suspects,
these precautions can protect you.
God forbid. I'll leave.
But tell me, how will you steal her?
Damián, the truck
is merging onto the freeway.
Go to your position.
We have visual. It's behind us.
Operation Swarm is underway.
What's Operation Swarm?
Something as simple
as sticking the truck in a bubble of cars
of our own creation.
The logistics are complex.
You'll need at least 19 vehicles.
Do you have drivers you trust?
People I trust completely.
My future wife.
I'm already behind the truck.
And my new in-laws.
In position.
- We are all set.
- Closing the convoy.
That truck will be the center
of our entourage.
Like the Virgin Mary in a procession.
But they'll just think
it's a Monday traffic jam,
caused by a watermelon truck.
Nothing looks less
like a sophisticated art heist
than a watermelon truck. Watermelons!
Where will you do it?
On the Triana Bridge. In broad daylight.
The Triana Bridge.
You chose a bridge to control
the only two access points.
Exactly.
And since we want no tragedies,
the first step will be to block
the bike and pedestrian lanes.
That way…
we'll have a clear lane.
Our procession will arrive
at the scene of the operation.
That will be when our magic trick begins.
I'm crazy about magic.
Ready, Roi?
Go ahead.
Our show starts with a tragic mishap
to grab our audience's attention.
A blown tire.
Let's fly.
Once the trucks form a barricade,
our symphony of screeching brakes
will commence.
The charges will be hidden in the cars.
They're like special-effects charges
used in movies.
These are the sensors.
A tiny tap, and…
We'll wrap the armored truck
in thick smoke and keep at it.
Dozens of pedestrians will think
they're witnessing a tragic accident.
But what we'll do
is direct their attention
from one point to another.
To keep them from thinking.
Back up! It's going to explode!
Move back!
While those retinas
go from explosion to explosion…
none of them will notice
that within that smoke,
midway across the bridge,
the greatest art heist in history
will be underway.
These are exact replicas
of an explosive device.
Impressive.
They won't risk opening the door
and blowing themselves up.
They're no Schwarzeneggers.
Neither Roberto Cornejo nor Blas Mencía
strike me as the type
to play hero and lose a limb,
defending Renaissance art.
The painting and its mount
measure 59 by 45 centimeters.
So we've built our own transport.
TRIANA PIZZAS
SEVILLE
We're getting the Lady with an Ermine out
in a pizza box?
That's right. With a deliveryman.
Pure genius.
Now comes the real stroke of genius.
When the Lady with an Ermine
is crossing Seville on a delivery bike,
some ruffians will start attacking
the truck with thermal lances.
We'll cut the steel at 3,500 degrees.
When we are halfway done with the job,
sirens will start wailing
in nearby streets.
We're leaving!
Everything will be meticulously calculated
so it looks like a rushed escape.
And when the police arrive in this chaos,
they'll struggle
to understand what's happening.
Suddenly, with the smoke
still floating over the bridge,
they'll start to figure it out.
10-79, attempted robbery.
Explosives! Everybody out! Let's go!
When at last they open the door
to the armored truck…
they will breathe a sigh of relief.
They'll see the Lady with an Ermine
in its security packaging.
Intact.
A perfect copy of the Lady with an Ermine.
That's why you visited the Dutchman.
Correct.
With that copy, we'll have made the swap.
It's a masterful copy.
The best that can be created
absent Leonardo da Vinci.
We've manufactured everything.
The packing tape, bulletproof crystal,
aluminum stand,
and even the ID codes for the piece.
The numbers are randomly generated
as soon as the piece leaves the museum.
How did you print those stickers
if the painting hasn't left Poland?
The software has some weaknesses
we harnessed to modify it without a trace.
Everything in order.
They will believe
it was an attempted theft gone wrong.
And they will believe it for a long time.
The plan is masterful, but…
where will the real
Lady with an Ermine be?
Strolling around Seville
in a bag from a department store.
The last place you'd think to look
for the loot of a theft
no one knows has happened.
…wicker baskets
for the Boletus edulis,
and they are so cute, with their…
AN HOUR LATER.
Breaking news from Seville,
where an attempted robbery
took place on Triana Bridge.
The robbers' objective
was Leonardo da Vinci's famous painting
Lady with an Ermine,
which will soon be exhibited
in the provincial capital.
So far there are no injuries reported.
They did it.
Do you hear me?
- She's mine.
- Congratulations, sir.
For a moment you almost confused me.
With your mediocrity.
And your loser mentality.
I was only trying to be prudent, sir.
Goodbye.
You go on. I'm leaving.
At the same time the duke
disconnected Santos,
our guard dog,
fate made dead men out of us
because of a loose end.
I see you brought your own bag.
How long have I been here?
Are you gonna talk?
Fine then, a bit more tequila.
So?
I don't have a fucking band.
And even if I did, I'd never tell you.
How are we doing?
There's no one 42 miles around.
That means you won't have the good fortune
of coming across another ship.
And the more you swim, the worse,
because you'll get tired
and lose more body heat.
The closest shore is Algeria,
370 miles away.
Give me something.
Who wants to betray my boss?
Or who wants to rob us?
Give me a little bit.
So we can defend ourselves, dammit.
It's that or a dive.
My boss is called Mr. Smalls.
Mr. Smalls?
What Mr. Smalls?
The one with the big balls.
You're a brat
with more arrogance than brains.
I'm gonna get out of the water.
I don't know how.
Hugging some fucking driftwood.
I'll resist everything.
And I swear we'll meet again.
We'll report your disappearance at dawn.
Until then, good luck.
Decoding in progress.
According to the georadar,
there's a cylinder under the vault.
As you can see from the color,
it contains methane.
Once the methane and oxygen
are consumed by the fire,
the deposits will be refilled.
Or not, we don't know
if they refill automatically
or if someone
would have to activate the system.
We don't know but we must consider it.
When I hack that door,
Bruce and Roi will go in
and there'll be an explosion
in the inner ring.
And whatever happens,
that door will only open once more
to exit with the money.
Or we'll face a second fireball
you won't survive.
Five digits.
I'm sorry,
but I don't have the guts to go in.
Bruce, don't go in.
We have the fireproof suits,
the oxygen and the helmets.
We could walk into hell itself
shouting and high on adrenaline.
- Roi…
- It's only 40 seconds, Bruce.
- Let's go.
- No, Roi.
You need to go in there
to get your adrenaline rush
and not feel like you're
the unhappiest man in the world.
Like one of those idiots
who does the opposite of what he feels.
Who, instead of being sad,
toasts with champagne
because his girlfriend left him.
Who, instead of running
from a ball of fire,
walks into it to avoid hearing his pain.
You're so pitiful
I don't know how to help you.
Don't either of you go in.
Hell, yes, a bit of clarity.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Two digits.
Damián, I'm going in.
- All clear?
- Free and clear.
Roi, don't be naive.
One missing.
Bruce! Bruce, no.
Bruce, don't go in! Bruce!
Bruce! Bruce, no!
Someone tell me what the hell's going on.
Both of them just went in.
What are we doing?
The ball of fire will ignite soon.
Roi, Bruce, do you hear me?
We're fine so far. The suit's holding.
Forty-five seconds.
Bruce, are you okay?
Bruce? The visor's fogging.
I don't see Bruce.
Thirty seconds.
Bruce! Are you okay?
Something's not okay. Fuck.
I'm burning.
Fuck, Roi!
Twenty-five seconds.
The oxygen tank is getting hot.
His leg's burning!
My back's burning up! Get us out of here!
- Twenty seconds.
- Let's go in.
Berlin, let's go in.
- Get us out of here!
- Don't open the door.
We can't open it.
The oxygen will stoke the fireball.
When it dies down I'll go in for them.
Open the door!
Fifteen seconds.
Keila!
Are you gonna let them die?
Jesus, we're being burned alive!
Open the door, for fuck's sake!
Open the door!
Ten seconds.
We have to wait.
Berlin, get us out of here, dammit!
Bruce!
Five.
They are dead.
- Four.
- They are dead.
Three.
Two.
One.
- Time!
- Keila, open.
You have a few seconds to get them out
before the door closes again.
Is that Roi?
Is it Bruce? Are they alive?
Berlin, hurry up. You don't have time.
Let's go.
I don't know if I can get up.
You can.
Berlin, it's gonna close!
Berlin!
The fireball will come back.
There's no gas coming out.
The methane didn't refill.
Roi is alive!
Let's go.
Berlin, how is Bruce?
Berlin?
Say something! Is he alive?
Fucking hell…
Bruce is alive.
My leg.
Oh, crap.
This time I got some serious damage.
Don't think about it now.
That makes two of us.
Up you come!
If we made it this far…
we're opening that damn door.
How much is there here?
Much more than in Ali Baba's cave.
Roi! Are you okay?
I'll wear fingerless mittens for life.
But diamond ones.
We left the palace not knowing
why our last loose end
had not spelled our ruin.
Why, when Samuel
found the tracker among the bills,
instead of getting his gun,
he put on his pajamas and went to bed.
At sunrise,
when we were already
500 km out of Seville,
the duke woke Samuel up in a fury
because we had emptied his vault.
I've been robbed!
They emptied the whole vault!
All the money, you understand?
All the money, because of you!
You told me no one would rob me!
So the next thing he did
was make a beeline
for his collection
and make sure it was still there.
My Rembrandt…
My Van Gogh…
My Cézanne…
My Modigliani…
They've taken my whole life.
Sir, look.
It's the real one.
They stole it for me.
For me.
Dear lord duke,
there you have your Lady with an Ermine,
as promised.
It cost you a bit more, that's true,
as I didn't appraise it
with precision before.
Today, that painting
is worth more than 350 million dollars
and we could get some more
if we put it up for auction.
I took the liberty
of raising my fee to the 75 million
in your vault.
Where are my paintings?
I don't give a shit
about the fucking dirty money.
I want my collection.
My collection!
Turn around now.
Please.
See that light?
That's it.
It means we're recording you.
We have proof that you're
the greatest criminal in art history.
And we have images of the diamonds
you traffic in your yachts.
Look. The photos are on your bed.
If you decide to take revenge on us
or anything should happen to us,
all of that will come to light.
You will no longer be an honorable person
and will spend
the rest of your days in jail.
I'm sure you don't want that,
so I propose a deal.
How about you keep
the Lady with an Ermine,
your yachts, your diamonds…
and I keep the rest?
That way we both win.
But if you want us to lose,
we both lose.
Sir!
The duchess.
She's gone.
"I never thought I could love someone else
with the same intensity and passion
with which I've loved you."
"I'm sorry to do this to you,
because you are
the most beautiful half of my life,
but there comes a day
when things come to an end."
"Today is that day. Genoveva."
Sir,
I'll round up a few men right now
and go after them.
I'll track them to the end of my days
and I swear I will find them.
No.
We are even.
Go and get some rest.
I'm very tired.
I need to lie down.
Bring the Lady with an Ermine over here.
I want to see her up close.
Stay with me.
Lie down here.
There was the answer
to why that bodyguard
had not given us away.
Love.
That's why he saw as a miracle
the chance of eliminating
in one fell swoop
all the things that separated him
from the duke.
His wife,
his millions,
his social class, his obsession with art…
He'd stop being a servant
and would be seen as the only man
on earth left by his side.
Samuel had always been there
and had let all of that happen.
It seems we'll have
to start from scratch, Samuel.
But you know what?
I love starting from scratch.
Of course,
Álvaro.
The afternoon we finally managed
to get together far from danger,
the band erupted in merriment.
We had managed to execute
two perfect robberies.
One of them,
a magisterial lesson in style.
The other almost killed us,
which is always an incentive
to celebrate life even more.
But at that moment,
we didn't yet know how much pain
a happy ending can hold.
…whose disappearance was reported
by the captain of the Rosa de los Mares.
The body of the sailor who fell overboard
from the luxury yacht has been found.
Rescue teams found it
55 nautical miles
from the island of Sardinia.
According to police sources,
this would be 23-year-old
Natalia Reyes Guzmán,
who signed up to work
on the recreational vessel
with no prior experience.
The autopsy determined
she was in a state of inebriation
when she fell overboard
and drowned at sea.
Hi, Roi.
It's Cameron.
I have no signal right now, so…
I guess you'll get this message
when the yacht makes port somewhere.
I am being held.
And I swear I'm not afraid.
There's one thing
I can't stop thinking about.
It's driving me crazy.
It's silly.
Because it's just one word.
But I find it almost impossible to say it.
Now I know Berlin was right.
That I'm an arrogant and conceited brat
who self-sabotages,
making everything seem difficult
when it actually is much simpler.
Like this word I never dared say to you.
Sorry.
If I had been brave enough
to say it to you when I should,
I probably wouldn't be here.
But the best part is…
I would've saved our relationship.
I'm sorry, Roi.
I'm so sorry.
I hope you can forgive me one day.
I forgive you.
I forgive you, Cameron.
Say what you must now.
- What do you want me to say?
- What you're thinking.
That I should have never
let her go undercover.
That I drove her to the gates of death
to compete
with a selfish eccentric
who's just like me.
And now I have a death
and two burn victims on my conscience.
Those are your boundaries.
They set us apart.
I can have a death on my conscience,
but you can't.
It's not all about you.
We are all where we chose to be.
Bruce, Roi…
Even Cameron.
They all made a choice.
I could be in Marbella
opening safety deposit boxes
and eating turrón all by myself,
but from these days in Seville…
I'll have more memories
than from all my years teaching.
Some…
of a pain
beyond measure.
But that comes with being alive.
And something
that I know now as well.
To live without looking back.
Thank you.
Hey…
if you want,
we can rob the boxes in Marbella.
I don't like Christmas
all that much either.
Sure.
Surprise heists are growing on me.
But first I need to ask you
for a bit of time.
A few weeks.
And invite you to a wedding.
How about we go to Sapporo
these Christmas holidays?
Shall we ski in Japan?
Isn't it a great plan?
Yeah, but I have a job in Marbella and…
A job?
Isn't the groom supposed
to greet the bride at the altar? You're…
Yes. But first
I need to ask you a few questions.
I'm actually a professor
of quantum mechanics.
You're a university professor?
Well, it's a distraction
I allow myself in my downtime
from thievery and the criminal world.
We're going to Sapporo.
The day you were
at the hotel with Camille,
I thought you had something
in your jacket pocket.
- It looked like panties.
- The ones in my pocket were antiques.
She brought them as a souvenir
of our time in Paris.
What's wrong? You seem a bit off.
I don't like weddings.
Or wedding figurines.
Or even less wedding cakes.
I'm not going anywhere near
this wedding cake.
Do weddings make you sad too?
It's all the emotion.
His friend from Paris, right?
Oui. Je suis l'ami.
- Enchantée.
- Enchanté.
Where's the Lady with an Ermine now?
A magician never reveals his secrets,
but I'll give you a clue.
If in the near future you hear
it sells well below its price,
get suspicious.
And what is its price?
Never under 400 million dollars.
Subtitle translation by:
Soledad Etchemendy